manifestation-miracle.org 2016-02-04

# Privacy Policy

**EFFECTIVE DATE:** 06\. 27. 2015 ****

1\. **INTRODUCTION**. manifestation-miracle.org (“us,” “we,” or “Manifestation-Miracle”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Manifestation-Miracle website landing page (the “Site”). We created this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.  
2\. **TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED AND USE**  
(a) **TRAFFIC DATA**. We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: (1) IP addresses; (2) browser type; (3) referring site link; (4) date and time the Site was visited; and (5) visitor location (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes. Traffic Data is collected through StatCounter.com and is used to track your behavior, target ads, and help you navigate through the Site.  
(b) **COOKIES**. “Cookies” are small text files we put in your browser to track your usage of the Site, but they don't tell us who you are. Once you close your browser the cookie terminates. We also use cookies to customize content specific to your interests. If you want to restrict or block the cookies that are set by the Site, you can do this through your browser settings.  
(c) **PERSONAL INFORMATION**. We will never collect any information that personally identifies you, such as your name, address, email address, and telephone number (“Personal Information”). However, your Personal Information may be collected by any third party websites that are linked to the Site.  
3\. **STORAGE, CONFIDENTIALITY, AND SECURITY OF TRAFFIC DATA**. Your Traffic Data is stored through a third party visitor analysis website, StatCounter, and is protected in accordance with their policies and procedures. Your Traffic Data will only be accessible by us by logging in at these third party websites with a username and password. We will keep your Traffic Data and our usernames and passwords for these third party websites private and will not share this information with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; or (c) enforce our Terms of Use.  
4\. **PUBLIC INFORMATION**. The Site contains links to third party websites, specifically ClickBank.com, an order processing website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.   
5\. **UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**. We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. 

Copyright 2015 - manifestation-miracle.org - All Rights Reserved
